Christmas Land is a tv movie, romance film directed by Sam Irvin.
Jules has just inherited a quaint magical Christmas-themed village and
Christmas tree farm bequeathed her by her grandmother.
She plans to sell it and use the profits to buy her dream home in New York City.
But the longer Jules stays on the farm and the more she learns how important Christmas Land has
been to so many families, the more Jules starts to question her motives to sell.
Jules Cooper, played by Nikki DeLoach.
Tucker Martin, played by Luke Macfarlane.
Glinda Bonaparte, played by Maureen McCormick.
Mason Richards, played by Richard Karn.
Gretchen, played by Chonda Pierce.
Elaine Richardson, played by Cynthia Gibb.
Almost Christmas is a 2016 American Christmas
comedy-drama film written and directed by David E.
Talbert and starring Kimberly Elise, Mo'Nique, Nicole Ari Parker, Gabrielle Union, Keri
Hilson, Jessie Usher, Danny Glover, Omar Epps, John Michael Higgins, D.C.
Young Fly, and Romany Malco.
The film follows a dysfunctional family that comes together for the
holidays for the first time since their mother's death.
Principal photography took place during November and
December 2015 in Covington, Georgia.
The film premiered in Los Angeles on November 3, 2016 and was theatrically released
in the United States on November 11, 2016 by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews and grossed $42 million.
The tone is emotional.